<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Workshops on SIPPS</title>
    <link>https://columbia-sipps.github.io/workshops/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Workshops on SIPPS</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://columbia-sipps.github.io/workshops/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Coding</title>
      <link>https://columbia-sipps.github.io/workshops/coding/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://columbia-sipps.github.io/workshops/coding/</guid>
      <description>On this page, you will find resources associated with each session in the coding workshop series. A few days before each session, please check this page to make sure you’ve downloaded any necessary files in advance (if needed). After each session, the page will be updated with links any additional materials/answer keys/etc. that were referenced during the workshop.
 Week 1: Setting up your R environment Before the workshop:   download these files: data file, RMarkdown file, R Project file  After the workshop:   RMarkdown file (with answers)   Note: If you have trouble knitting your Rmd file, find the code chunk where you load in a set of packages (using the library() function), and remove the text eval = False.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Professional Development / Journal Club</title>
      <link>https://columbia-sipps.github.io/workshops/development/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://columbia-sipps.github.io/workshops/development/</guid>
      <description>On this page, you will find resources associated with the Professional Development/Journal Club workshop series. Before each journal club session, check this page for details about which article that will be discussed. After each session in the series, the page will be updated with any additional materials that were referenced during the workshop.
 Week 1: Panel with past SIPPS students 
No additional workshop materials.
  Week 2: How to read a scientific paper</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research Skills</title>
      <link>https://columbia-sipps.github.io/workshops/research_skills/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://columbia-sipps.github.io/workshops/research_skills/</guid>
      <description>On this page, you will find resources associated with the Research Skills workshop series. Before each session, check this page for any resources you should download prior to the workshop. After each session in the series, the page will be updated with any additional materials that were referenced during the workshop.
 Week 1: What is a good research question? Workshop materials:   Workshop slides    Week 2: Literature search &amp;amp; Zotero Workshop materials:   Workshop slides    Week 3: Organizing your research Before the workshop:   Please download (and unzip) this set of files: learnShell.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
