<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>SIPPS</title>
    <link>https://columbia-sipps.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on SIPPS</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://columbia-sipps.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Coding</title>
      <link>https://columbia-sipps.github.io/workshops/coding/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://columbia-sipps.github.io/workshops/coding/</guid>
      <description>Workshop materials for SIPPS 2023 will be posted as the workshop series unfolds this upcoming summer. For workshop materials from previous years of SIPPS, please follow this link.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coding (2022)</title>
      <link>https://columbia-sipps.github.io/workshops2022/coding/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://columbia-sipps.github.io/workshops2022/coding/</guid>
      <description>See below for resources associated with the coding workshops from SIPPS 2022. For materials from other years and/or workshop series, follow this link.
 Week 1: Setting up your R environment Before the workshop:   download these files: data file, RMarkdown file, R Project file  After the workshop:   RMarkdown file (with answers)   Note: If you have trouble knitting your Rmd file, find the code chunk where you load in a set of packages (using the library() function), and remove the text eval = False.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coding: Basic (2021)</title>
      <link>https://columbia-sipps.github.io/workshops2021/coding_basic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://columbia-sipps.github.io/workshops2021/coding_basic/</guid>
      <description>See below for resources associated with the basic-track coding workshops from SIPPS 2021. For materials from other years and/or workshop series, follow this link.
 Week 1: Setting up your R environment Before the workshop:   download these files: data file, RMarkdown file, R Project file  After the workshop:   RMarkdown key    Week 2: Programming fundamentals Before the workshop:   please create a folder named 02_intro-programming on your computer  download these files within that folder: data file (shakes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coding: Advanced (2021)</title>
      <link>https://columbia-sipps.github.io/workshops2021/coding_advanced/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://columbia-sipps.github.io/workshops2021/coding_advanced/</guid>
      <description>See below for resources associated with the advanced-track coding workshops from SIPPS 2021. For materials from other years and/or workshop series, follow this link.
 Week 1: Refresher of regression and moderation (frequentist) Before the workshop:   make sure you have both R and RStudio downloaded on your machine; if you don’t, check out this page for guidance  Workshop materials:   R packages used today: tidyverse (contains ggplot2, dplyr, and others); car  intro to regression slides  RMarkdown lesson file (with notes)  RMarkdown challenge file / answer key</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Professional Development / Journal Club</title>
      <link>https://columbia-sipps.github.io/workshops/development/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://columbia-sipps.github.io/workshops/development/</guid>
      <description>Workshop materials for SIPPS 2023 will be posted as the workshop series unfolds this upcoming summer. For workshop materials from previous years of SIPPS, please follow this link.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Professional Development / Journal Club (2021)</title>
      <link>https://columbia-sipps.github.io/workshops2021/development/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://columbia-sipps.github.io/workshops2021/development/</guid>
      <description>See below for resources associated with the professional development &amp;amp; journal club workshops from SIPPS 2021. For materials from other years and/or workshop series, follow this link.
 Week 1: What is a good research question? Workshop materials:   workshop slides  link to collaborative brainstorming Google Doc    Week 2: Careers inside and outside academia Workshop materials:   workshop slides    Week 3: Journal club Workshop materials:   This week’s reading: Variety Wins: Soccer-Playing Robots and Infant Walking (Ossmy et al.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Professional Development / Journal Club (2022)</title>
      <link>https://columbia-sipps.github.io/workshops2022/development/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://columbia-sipps.github.io/workshops2022/development/</guid>
      <description>See below for resources associated with the professional development &amp;amp; journal club workshops from SIPPS 2022. For materials from other years and/or workshop series, follow this link.
 Week 1: Panel with past SIPPS students 
No additional materials.
  Week 2: How to read a scientific paper 
Workshop materials:
  Literature review spreadsheet template  QuALMRI overview  QuALMRI literature review outline  Godden &amp;amp; Baddeley (1975)  Kirkham et al.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research Skills</title>
      <link>https://columbia-sipps.github.io/workshops/research_skills/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://columbia-sipps.github.io/workshops/research_skills/</guid>
      <description>Workshop materials for SIPPS 2023 will be posted as the workshop series unfolds this upcoming summer. For workshop materials from previous years of SIPPS, please follow this link.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research Skills (2021)</title>
      <link>https://columbia-sipps.github.io/workshops2021/research_skills/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://columbia-sipps.github.io/workshops2021/research_skills/</guid>
      <description>See below for resources associated with the research skills workshops from SIPPS 2021. For materials from other years and/or workshop series, follow this link.
 Week 1: How to make the most of your summer experience (Dr. Valerie Purdie-Greenaway) Workshop materials:   workshop slides    Week 2: Literature search &amp;amp; Zotero Workshop materials:   workshop slides    Week 3: Pre-registration &amp;amp; OSF Workshop materials:   Workshop slides  Activity Readme  Datafile  OSF Pre-registration template    Week 4: Git (Version control &amp;amp; script sharing) Before the workshop:   Please download this file (Git installation instructions), and follow the instructions to install git  Sign up for an account on github.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research Skills (2022)</title>
      <link>https://columbia-sipps.github.io/workshops2022/research_skills/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://columbia-sipps.github.io/workshops2022/research_skills/</guid>
      <description>See below for resources associated with the research skills workshops from SIPPS 2022. For materials from other years and/or workshop series, follow this link.
 Week 1: What is a good research question? Workshop materials:   Workshop slides    Week 2: Literature search &amp;amp; Zotero Workshop materials:   Workshop slides    Week 3: Organizing your research Before the workshop:   Please download (and unzip) this set of files: learnShell.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About the SIPPS Program</title>
      <link>https://columbia-sipps.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://columbia-sipps.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>→ What is SIPPS?  SIPPS is a 10-week summer program hosted within Columbia University’s Psychology department that aims to provide Columbia undergraduate and post-bac students with an immersive and practical introduction to psychological research. The SIPPS curriculum comprises two main components: (1) multiple weekly workshops, which involve hands-on training in practical research methods and tools (e.g., statistical analysis and coding, experimental design, and literature reviews); and (2) a mentored research experience, under the supervision of a graduate student or postdoctoral mentor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apply</title>
      <link>https://columbia-sipps.github.io/apply/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://columbia-sipps.github.io/apply/</guid>
      <description>SIPPS 2023 applications are now closed!   Decisions were sent out during the first few weeks of May. However, we’ve been notified that some of our emails are being mistakenly marked as spam. If you have not received a decision email, please check your spam folder, and reach out to sippscupsych@gmail.com if nothing is there.
 
 Important Program Details    SIPPS 2023 will run from June 12 to August 18.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diversity Statement</title>
      <link>https://columbia-sipps.github.io/diversity/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://columbia-sipps.github.io/diversity/</guid>
      <description>The SIPPS team comprises a group of graduate students, post-docs, undergraduates, and faculty advisors who are committed to diversity and inclusion, in its broadest sense. We are scientists whose day-to-day research seeks to understand how people think, behave, and relate to one other and how differences in our experiences, both positive and adverse, affect our brain, relationships, and behavior. Our work encompasses and embraces the ideas of diversity and support.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Instructor Materials</title>
      <link>https://columbia-sipps.github.io/instructors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://columbia-sipps.github.io/instructors/</guid>
      <description>Quick links for graduate students, postdocs, and staff in charge of putting on the SIPPS program. Please disregard if you are a participant in this program. Please contact Manasi if you are unable to access any of the links below.    instructor schedule  guidelines for instructors  guidelines for mentored research experience  mentor/mentee contract  post-workshop exit survey (link coming soon)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meet the SIPPS Team</title>
      <link>https://columbia-sipps.github.io/team/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://columbia-sipps.github.io/team/</guid>
      <description>SIPPS is a program developed &amp;amp; run primarily by graduate students, postdocs, and staff in Columbia’s Psychology Department.
Core Team  CJ Concepcion is a PhD student in the Couples Lab. She is interested in the physiological mechanisms that underlie cross-group interactions and how we can mitigate potential socioemotional and health consequences when such interactions are negative (i.e., experiencing discrimination).  email   Ana DiGiovanni is a PhD student in the Couples Lab.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>https://columbia-sipps.github.io/resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://columbia-sipps.github.io/resources/</guid>
      <description>On this page you will find an assortment of miscellaneous resources that you may find useful as a student interested in psychological research. Please note that all materials developed for specific workshop sessions will instead be found on the workshops page. Don’t hesitate to reach out to your mentor(s) and/or your instructors with specific questions about these resources.  Summer Research Funding   See this spreadsheet for a list of summer funding opportunities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Schedule</title>
      <link>https://columbia-sipps.github.io/schedule/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://columbia-sipps.github.io/schedule/</guid>
      <description>SIPPS hosts three parallel workshop series, each with one session per week. See below for a detailed overview of all workshop topics and dates, and see the workshops page for materials associated with each session.
Before each workshop, make sure to review any pre-workshop recordings &amp;amp; materials here!
Professional Development  Mondays, 11am-12pm Zoom links sent via email.   Coding  Wednesdays, 11am-12pm Zoom links sent via email.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SIPPS Mini-Conference</title>
      <link>https://columbia-sipps.github.io/pastsipps/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://columbia-sipps.github.io/pastsipps/</guid>
      <description>Check out the presentations made by previous SIPPS participants during our end-of-summer conference!  
  SIPPS 2022    Suppression of competing information during memory-guided attention Shelton Brister
Mentor: Serra Favila

 The impact of emotional valence on memory SooYeon Choi
Mentors: Camille Gasser, John Thorp, &amp;amp; Wangjing Yu

 How do beliefs about social regulation predict the quality and quantity of our social network?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
