<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Workshops (2021) on SIPPS</title>
    <link>https://columbia-sipps.github.io/workshops2021/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Workshops (2021) on SIPPS</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://columbia-sipps.github.io/workshops2021/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Coding (basic) - 2021</title>
      <link>https://columbia-sipps.github.io/workshops2021/coding_basic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://columbia-sipps.github.io/workshops2021/coding_basic/</guid>
      <description>See below for resources associated with the basic-track coding workshops from SIPPS 2021. For other workshops from 2021, follow this link.
 Week 1: Setting up your R environment  View Recording  Before the workshop:   download these files: data file, RMarkdown file, R Project file  After the workshop:   RMarkdown key    Week 2: Programming fundamentals  View Recording  Before the workshop:   please create a folder named 02_intro-programming on your computer  download these files within that folder: data file (shakes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coding (advanced) - 2021</title>
      <link>https://columbia-sipps.github.io/workshops2021/coding_advanced/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://columbia-sipps.github.io/workshops2021/coding_advanced/</guid>
      <description>See below for resources associated with the advanced-track coding workshops from SIPPS 2021. For other workshops from 2021, follow this link.
 Week 1: Refresher of regression and moderation (frequentist)  View Recording  Before the workshop:   make sure you have both R and RStudio downloaded on your machine; if you don’t, check out this page for guidance  Workshop materials:   R packages used today: tidyverse (contains ggplot2, dplyr, and others); car  intro to regression slides  RMarkdown lesson file (with notes)  RMarkdown challenge file / answer key</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Professional Development / Journal Club - 2021</title>
      <link>https://columbia-sipps.github.io/workshops2021/development/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://columbia-sipps.github.io/workshops2021/development/</guid>
      <description>See below for resources associated with the professional development/journal club workshop track from SIPPS 2021. For other workshops from 2021, follow this link.  Week 1: What is a good research question?  View Recording  Workshop materials:   workshop slides  link to collaborative brainstorming Google Doc    Week 2: Careers inside and outside academia  View Recording  Workshop materials:   workshop slides    Week 3: Journal club  View Recording  Workshop materials:   This week’s reading: Variety Wins: Soccer-Playing Robots and Infant Walking (Ossmy et al.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research Skills - 2021</title>
      <link>https://columbia-sipps.github.io/workshops2021/research_skills/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://columbia-sipps.github.io/workshops2021/research_skills/</guid>
      <description>See below for resources associated with the research skills workshop series from SIPPS 2021. For other workshops from 2021, follow this link.
 Week 1: How to make the most of your summer experience (Dr. Valerie Purdie-Greenaway)  View Recording  Workshop materials:   workshop slides    Week 2: Literature search &amp;amp; Zotero  View Recording  Workshop materials:   workshop slides    Week 3: Pre-registration &amp;amp; OSF  View Recording  Workshop materials:   Workshop slides  Activity Readme  Datafile  OSF Pre-registration template    Week 4: Git (Version control &amp;amp; script sharing)  View Recording</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
