<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Workshops on SIPPS</title>
    <link>/workshops/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Workshops on SIPPS</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/workshops/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Coding (basic)</title>
      <link>/workshops/coding_basic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/workshops/coding_basic/</guid>
      <description> On this page, you will find resources associated with each session in the basic-track coding workshop. A few days before each session, please check this page to make sure you’ve downloaded any necessary files in advance (if needed). After each session, the page will be updated with links to the corresponding zoom recording, as well as any additional materials/answer keys/etc. that were referenced during the workshop.  Week 1: Setting up your R environment Before the workshop:   download these files: data file, RMarkdown file, R Project file  After the workshop:   RMarkdown key   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coding (advanced)</title>
      <link>/workshops/coding_advanced/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/workshops/coding_advanced/</guid>
      <description>On this page, you will find resources associated with each session in the advanced-track coding workshop. A few days before each session, please check this page to make sure you’ve downloaded any necessary files in advance (if needed). After each session, the page will be updated with links to the corresponding zoom recording, as well as any additional materials/answer keys/etc. that were referenced during the workshop.  Week 1: Refresher of regression and moderators (frequentist) Before the workshop:   Make sure you have both R and RStudio downloaded on your machine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Professional Development / Journal Club</title>
      <link>/workshops/development/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/workshops/development/</guid>
      <description>Coming soon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research Skills</title>
      <link>/workshops/research_skills/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/workshops/research_skills/</guid>
      <description>Coming soon.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
